isedb.com 2005-04-05

# Privacy Policy - The Internet Search Engine Database - ISEDB.com

In general, The Internet Search Engine Database(ISEDB.COM) does not collect, store, use or disclose personally identifying information The instances in which ISEDB does collect and use information are specifically described in this Privacy Policy.   
ISEDB provides fun, easy to use services, including ISEDB directory (located at WWW.ISEDB.COM). This service may also be located on third party web sites and/or applications. ISEDB values its users and their concerns about privacy.   

**What does this Privacy Policy cover?**  
This Privacy Policy applies to collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by ISEDB. If there are any exceptions, we will clearly disclose them prior to collecting any information, and will give you an opportunity to choose not to participate or provide the information.   
ISEDB provides links to Web sites operated by third parties. ISEDB is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party Web sites or applications. Also, please be aware that banner ads on ISEDB are provided by a third party, which may collect cookies as part of the process of serving those ads. These cookies are typically used for the purpose of tracking performance of the banner ads, for proper directing of click through and statistical tracking. ISEDB does not determine which information will be collected by that third party.

**Third Party Banner Ads.**  
We use other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

**What information does ISEDB collect and how is it used? Does ISEDB disclose information to third parties?**  
ISEDB may collect any or all of the following three types of information:   
Data about traffic and usage is not personally identifying or identifiable, and is not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information. Whenever you request a page, your IP address, browser and version, operating system and the site you came from are stored in a log file. This information cannot be used to identify a specific individual. This information is only used for statistical purposes to help improve this site and provide accurate statistics to advertisers in the form of aggregated data. This information is kept on a secure server. ISEDB may share information it collects with certain selected third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form.   
**Cookies**. Like many sites, ISEDB collects information about online behavior using cookies. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site and how frequently they are returning, as well as to streamline their experiences using the Services. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Cookies lets us know about repeat visitors and if we are delivering quality products and services. ISEDB may also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites, and can, where necessary, pay our affiliates and other business partners. To ISEDB, using information within cookies is an anonymous way to survey how we are doing and to look for ways to improve our services. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to use all of the features of the services. ISEDB may share information about usage of the services with third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Email, Contact Information or Personally Identifying Information.**   
ISEDB can obtain access to your name, e-mail address and other contact information only 

  * when you become an advertiser with ISEDB, provide comments, submit a problem, or request information from ISEDB and provide your name or return contact information
  * Connection with special offers or contests.   

  * The email addresses collected from the sign-ups for our mailing list are not sold, or disclosed to a third party. The email addresses collected will only be used to send out the newsletter/promotions from our merchants. You will not receive any mailings you did not request. You can remove yourself from our list by following the instruction we provide when we send emails.

Contact information provided in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests. This information is not stored or used in connection with traffic or clickstream data and is provided to a third party only as necessary to respond to the comment, problem or request. 

Finally, you may choose to provide contact information, other personally identifying information, and demographic information in order to participate in optional surveys or contests, which are run for promotional purposes. ISEDB uses such information to send you information about its products and to notify you if you win the contest. Finally, from time to time, but only with your permission, ISEDB may provide certain of its users' registration information to selected third parties who wish to participate in special promotions offered in conjunction with ISEDB. Users may opt-out of receiving such communications at any time by contacting ISEDB. 

Questions regarding our privacy policies, and for assistance in opting out of our email lists please contact us
